15 years ago near Qinghe Orphanage
I've seen you
This item
Do you still remember it
As long as I take that place from back then
Things can still turn around
Who is this
Mr. Fu, it's me, Su Yurou
15 years ago near Qinghe Orphanage
I saved an injured boy
He had a crescent-shaped scar on his wrist
You're saying that person was me
I'm not entirely sure
But seeing your old scar reminded me
Where did you get this
I've kept it all this time
That ginkgo leaf pendant
Was something on you back then
If this has to do with your past
I can't pretend not to know
10 AM tomorrow
Lu Group reception room
You're willing to see me
Bring the item
Sister, this time
I won't let you beat me to it
Who was it
Your sister
That pendant and the hospital receipt
Were from my old box